{
    "subject": "resource/Gianfranco_Giachetti",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Rome",
    "human_readable": "Gianfranco Giachetti died in Rome.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9018430709838867,
            "question": "Where did Gianfranco Giachetti die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8863503932952881,
            "question": "When did Gianfranco Giachetti die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7161359786987305,
            "question": "What city is known for being the location of Gianfranco Giachetti's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6150757074356079,
            "question": "Was Gianfranco Giachetti an Italian citizen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4707834720611572,
            "question": "What is Gianfranco Giachetti known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46120840311050415,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Gianfranco Giachetti's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43352755904197693,
            "question": "What was Gianfranco Giachetti's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3811686933040619,
            "question": "Is there anything else you know about Gianfranco Giachetti?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33860963582992554,
            "question": "Were there any notable achievements by Gianfranco Giachetti?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27642783522605896,
            "question": "Do you have any information about Gianfranco Giachetti's family?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gianfranco Giachetti died in Rome.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5033_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable achievements by Gianfranco Giachetti?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5033_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else you know about Gianfranco Giachetti?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5033_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Gianfranco Giachetti's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5033_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5033_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5033_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5033_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5033_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5033_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5033_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5033_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5033_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5033_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5033_51.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple \"Gianfranco Giachetti died in Rome\":\n\n`{ \"output\": \"yes\" }`\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all four relevant documents mention that Gianfranco Giachetti died on November 29, 1936, and that he died in Rome, Lazio, Italy."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents support the statement that Gianfranco Giachetti died in Rome, as it is explicitly mentioned in multiple files."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}